<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Democracy on Join EU</title>
    <link>https://ukjoineu.org/tags/democracy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Democracy on Join EU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:14:34 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ukjoineu.org/tags/democracy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>EU referendum broke code of good practice</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/referendum/venice-commision/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:14:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/referendum/venice-commision/</guid>
      <description>Referendum result &amp;lsquo;unsafe&amp;rsquo; Leave.eu has been fined the maximum amount possible by the Electoral Commission for multiple breaches of electoral rules. Other leave organisations have also been convicted of breaking electoral law.
Given that the UK is one of the 61 member states of the Commission and helped to form the Code, which was adopted in 2006. Proper adoption of this code would enable the Electoral Commision to annul an election or referendum if serious irregularities may have affected the result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals and values of the EU</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 17:37:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-goals/</guid>
      <description>Goals The goals of the European Union are:
 promote peace, its values and the well-being of its citizens offer freedom, security and justice without internal borders sustainable development based on balanced economic growth and price stability, a highly competitive market economy with full employment and social progress, and environmental protection combat social exclusion and discrimination promote scientific and technological progress enhance economic, social and territorial cohesion and solidarity among EU countries respect its rich cultural and linguistic diversity establish an economic and monetary union whose currency is the euro.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>