<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Join EU</title>
    <link>https://ukjoineu.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Join EU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:14:34 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ukjoineu.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 13:50:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/about/</guid>
      <description>During the Vietnam War the great pacifist A.J.Muste stood in front of the White House night after night with a candle.
Asked &amp;ldquo;Do you really think you&#39;ll change the country this way?&amp;rdquo;
Muste answered &amp;ldquo;I don&#39;t do this to change the country. I do this so the country won&#39;t change me.&amp;rdquo;
This is my purpose in creating this web site.
I remain committed to the UK being part of the EU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU referendum broke code of good practice</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/referendum/venice-commision/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:14:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/referendum/venice-commision/</guid>
      <description>Referendum result &amp;lsquo;unsafe&amp;rsquo; Leave.eu has been fined the maximum amount possible by the Electoral Commission for multiple breaches of electoral rules. Other leave organisations have also been convicted of breaking electoral law.
Given that the UK is one of the 61 member states of the Commission and helped to form the Code, which was adopted in 2006. Proper adoption of this code would enable the Electoral Commision to annul an election or referendum if serious irregularities may have affected the result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reasons for joining and staying in EEC</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/referendum1975/eec-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 17:19:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/referendum1975/eec-comments/</guid>
      <description>On joining EEC Ted Heath Ted Heath makes clear in December 1972 that we are joining something that is far more than a common market.
Harold Wilson &amp;ldquo;The lead Britain can give rests on the fact that we are a world-minded people. Britain will give a lead in political attitudes and political developments in Europe. We cannot do that by taking our bat home and sinking into an off-shore island mentality&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU Myths</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/referendum/eu-myths/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 16:08:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/referendum/eu-myths/</guid>
      <description>EU Myths One of the pre-referendum problems was the 40 years of deliberate lies about the EU perpetuated by the British press and other media outlets.
One of the useful things that EU officials did over the years from 1992 to 2017 was to document these myths and rebut them by providing the actual sequence of events or the true facts of the case.
See the following link for the full list which runs to 100s of entries &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals and values of the EU</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 17:37:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-goals/</guid>
      <description>Goals The goals of the European Union are:
 promote peace, its values and the well-being of its citizens offer freedom, security and justice without internal borders sustainable development based on balanced economic growth and price stability, a highly competitive market economy with full employment and social progress, and environmental protection combat social exclusion and discrimination promote scientific and technological progress enhance economic, social and territorial cohesion and solidarity among EU countries respect its rich cultural and linguistic diversity establish an economic and monetary union whose currency is the euro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eurobarometer</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eurobarometer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 10:39:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eurobarometer/</guid>
      <description>Human rights, freedom of speech, gender equality top lists of EU fundamental values 52% consider climate change to be the most current pressing environmental issue 59% are in favour of their country being a member of the EU  This Eurobarometer survey, published in December, asked citizens, among several topics, which political issue the Parliament should deal with as a matter of priority.
Parliament’s autumn Eurobarometer survey traditionally asks citizens which political issue the European Parliament should deal with as a matter of priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Pillar of Social Rights</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-social-rights/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 10:31:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-social-rights/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Today we commit ourselves to a set of 20 principles and rights. From the right to fair wages to the right to health care; from lifelong learning, a better work-life balance and gender equality to minimum income: with the European Pillar of Social Rights, the EU stands up for the rights of its citizens in a fast-changing world.&amp;rdquo;
  President Juncker on the proclamation of the European Pillar of Social Rights, 17 November 2017</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU New Green Deal</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-new-green-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 17:26:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-new-green-deal/</guid>
      <description>EU eases the costs of going green The European Union has unveiled details of its 1-trillion euro Green New Deal designed to cut emissions and move to a more climate friendly economy.
European Commission chief Ursula Von der Leyen has made the fight against climate change a priority and all EU countries except Poland have agreed they should transform their economies over the next 30 years.
Poland, which produces around 80 per cent of its power from coal, says it needs more guarantees on funding before agreeing to Europe’s new 2050 objective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU Trade</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-trade-deals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 11:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-trade-deals/</guid>
      <description>Single Market The single market is a huge benefit to all member states &amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip; is an extract from this report &amp;hellip; (http://www.amchameu.eu/sites/default/files/amcham_eu_single_market_web.pdf)
Trade deals Here is a link to the official EU page on trade agreements &amp;hellip; (https://ec.europa.eu/trade/policy/countries-and-regions/negotiations-and-agreements/index_en.htm)
A full list of countries and their trade status &amp;hellip; (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/European_Union_free_trade_agreements)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU Citizen Benefits</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-citizen-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 15:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-citizen-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Peace &amp;amp; Security Central and western Europe has never known so long a period without war. The EU is the most successful peace project in human history and has been awarded the Nobel Peace Prize. Europeans are closely linked economically and culturally, and through the democratic values we share.
Single Market The single market is the world&#39;s most highly developed and open marketplace. It is based on the EU’s 4 key freedoms, which enable you and other citizens to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annotated EU Flag</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-flag-annotated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 15:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-flag-annotated/</guid>
      <description>Here is a rather cheerful way of showing the EU flag and encompassing all the benefits of membership</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU rules imposed on UK</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/referendum/eu-rules-imposed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 14:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/referendum/eu-rules-imposed/</guid>
      <description>Lots of rubbish in the campaign about the EU imposing rules on us and not a lot about the fact that we agreed with nearly all of them and for those few we opposed we were always on the wrong side of the argument.
Fortunately, someone has done the hard work and anaylsed all of the individual laws and provided a neat summary on Twitter.
 EU laws A breakdown of all the EU laws that we have adopted and a list of those we opposed &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>https://ukjoineu.org/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ukjoineu.org/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>