<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Join EU</title>
    <link>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Join EU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 17:37:49 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ukjoineu.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals and values of the EU</title>
      <link>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 17:37:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-goals/</guid>
      <description>Goals The goals of the European Union are:
 promote peace, its values and the well-being of its citizens offer freedom, security and justice without internal borders sustainable development based on balanced economic growth and price stability, a highly competitive market economy with full employment and social progress, and environmental protection combat social exclusion and discrimination promote scientific and technological progress enhance economic, social and territorial cohesion and solidarity among EU countries respect its rich cultural and linguistic diversity establish an economic and monetary union whose currency is the euro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eurobarometer</title>
      <link>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eurobarometer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 10:39:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eurobarometer/</guid>
      <description>Human rights, freedom of speech, gender equality top lists of EU fundamental values 52% consider climate change to be the most current pressing environmental issue 59% are in favour of their country being a member of the EU  This Eurobarometer survey, published in December, asked citizens, among several topics, which political issue the Parliament should deal with as a matter of priority.
Parliament’s autumn Eurobarometer survey traditionally asks citizens which political issue the European Parliament should deal with as a matter of priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Pillar of Social Rights</title>
      <link>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-social-rights/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 10:31:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-social-rights/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Today we commit ourselves to a set of 20 principles and rights. From the right to fair wages to the right to health care; from lifelong learning, a better work-life balance and gender equality to minimum income: with the European Pillar of Social Rights, the EU stands up for the rights of its citizens in a fast-changing world.&amp;rdquo;
  President Juncker on the proclamation of the European Pillar of Social Rights, 17 November 2017</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU New Green Deal</title>
      <link>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-new-green-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 17:26:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-new-green-deal/</guid>
      <description>EU eases the costs of going green The European Union has unveiled details of its 1-trillion euro Green New Deal designed to cut emissions and move to a more climate friendly economy.
European Commission chief Ursula Von der Leyen has made the fight against climate change a priority and all EU countries except Poland have agreed they should transform their economies over the next 30 years.
Poland, which produces around 80 per cent of its power from coal, says it needs more guarantees on funding before agreeing to Europe’s new 2050 objective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU Trade</title>
      <link>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-trade-deals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 11:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-trade-deals/</guid>
      <description>Single Market The single market is a huge benefit to all member states &amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip; is an extract from this report &amp;hellip; (http://www.amchameu.eu/sites/default/files/amcham_eu_single_market_web.pdf)
Trade deals Here is a link to the official EU page on trade agreements &amp;hellip; (https://ec.europa.eu/trade/policy/countries-and-regions/negotiations-and-agreements/index_en.htm)
A full list of countries and their trade status &amp;hellip; (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/European_Union_free_trade_agreements)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU Citizen Benefits</title>
      <link>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-citizen-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 15:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-citizen-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Peace &amp;amp; Security Central and western Europe has never known so long a period without war. The EU is the most successful peace project in human history and has been awarded the Nobel Peace Prize. Europeans are closely linked economically and culturally, and through the democratic values we share.
Single Market The single market is the world&#39;s most highly developed and open marketplace. It is based on the EU’s 4 key freedoms, which enable you and other citizens to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annotated EU Flag</title>
      <link>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-flag-annotated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 15:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/eu-flag-annotated/</guid>
      <description>Here is a rather cheerful way of showing the EU flag and encompassing all the benefits of membership</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reasons to be pro EU</title>
      <link>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/reasons-pro-eu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 15:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ukjoineu.org/posts/reasons-pro-eu/</guid>
      <description>Here is a good list of reasons to be Pro EU &amp;hellip;
I am not Pro EU as default.
I&amp;#39;m...
Pro Peace
Pro Cooperation
Pro Good Friday Agreement
Pro Immigration
Pro Science
Pro Security
Pro Education
Pro Business
Pro Trade
Pro Human Rights
Pro Workers Rights
Pro NHS
Pro Multi-Cultural
All these thing mean I am automatically Pro EU.
&amp;mdash; 🔶️Chantelle Seddon (@ChantelleSeddon) January 10, 2020  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>